pcspeedboost.com 2015-05-25

# PC SpeedBoost — Clean Up Your PC

Your privacy is important to Boost Software, Inc. ("Boost"). This Privacy Policy describes the information practices for the Boost Sites, including what type of information is gathered and tracked, how the information is used, and with whom the information is shared. As described below, this statement also applies to your other interactions with Boost, such as when you license software subject to an End-User License Agreement or enter into Terms of Service for a Boost offering, or provide information to Boost at a trade show or other event. 

**What Information We Collect:** This Privacy Policy applies to all information collected by or submitted to Boost (or carefully selected third parties acting on Boost's behalf), including personal information. "Personal information" is data that reasonably can be used to identify or describe an individual. You do not need to provide us personal information to simply browse our site or to download certain limited functionality software.

**Boost may collect personal information when:**

  * you make purchases of products or services;
  * you register products online;
  * you request support for a Boost product;
  * you request free software downloads;
  * you create a user account (login user name and password) on a Boost Site;
  * you register for webcasts, seminars and roundtables;
  * you request information or materials (e.g., whitepapers or newsletters);
  * you participate in surveys and evaluations;
  * you participate in promotions, contests or giveaways;
  * you apply for a job, or submit your resume to Boost;
  * you submit questions or comments to us.

Boost may also collect personal information from individuals (with their consent) at conventions, trade shows and expositions.

**The types of personal information collected may include (but are not limited to):**

  * your first and last name;
  * your title and your company's name;
  * your home, billing, or other physical address (including street name, name of a city or town, state/province, postal code);
  * your e-mail address;
  * your telephone number;
  * (for job applicants submitting electronic information) your educational background, employment experience, and job interest;
  * any other identifier that permits Boost to make physical or online contact with you;
  * any information that Boost collects online from you and maintains in association with your account, such as: (a) your Boost username, (b) your Boost password, and/or (c) your credit card account information.

**Use of Your Personal Information:** Boost collects and uses your personal information to operate and improve its sites and deliver the services or carry out the transactions you have requested. These uses may include providing you with more effective customer service; making the sites or services easier to use by eliminating the need for you to repeatedly enter the same information; performing research and analysis aimed at improving our products, services and technologies; and displaying content and advertising that are customized to your interests and preferences.

We also use your personal information to communicate with you. We may send certain mandatory service communications such as welcome letters, billing reminders, information on technical service issues, and security announcements. Some Boost services may send periodic member letters that are considered part of the service. We may also contact you to inform you of other products or services available from Boost and its affiliates if you specifically opt-in to receive such communications from us.

Personal information collected on Boost Sites and services may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Boost or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using a Boost Site or service, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.

**Sharing of Your Personal Information:** Boost will not sell, rent or lease your personal information to others. Boost shares personal information with companies working on our behalf and Boost-owned business entities. Except as described in this statement, we will not disclose your personal information to third parties for their own marketing purposes unless you have provided consent.

Some Boost services may be co-branded and offered in conjunction with another company. If you register for or use such services, both Boost and the other company may receive information collected as part of the co-branded services.

In some cases Boost uses contractors to collect, use, analyze and otherwise process information on its behalf. It is Boost's practice to require such suppliers to handle information in a manner consistent with Boost's policies. 

If you request something from a Boost Site (for example, a product or service, a callback, or specific marketing materials), we will use the information you provide to fulfill your request. To help us do this, we may share information with others, such as Boost's business partners, financial institutions, shipping companies, and postal or government authorities (e.g., Customs authorities) involved in fulfillment. As part of a transaction, we may also contact you as part of our customer satisfaction surveys or for market research purposes.

We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as handling the processing and delivery of mailings, providing customer support, hosting websites, processing transactions, or performing statistical analysis of our services. Those companies will be permitted to obtain only the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information and are prohibited from using it for any other purpose.

We may access and/or disclose your personal information if we believe such action is necessary to: (a) comply with the law or legal process served on Boost; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Boost (including the enforcement of our agreements); or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Boost services or members of the public.

**Your Choices:** Boost provides a number of ways for you to 'opt-out' of receiving additional information from us or having us provide your personal information to our partners. We may offer you these choices at the time you give us your information. 

If you do not wish to continue receiving certain marketing materials (e.g., e-mail messages), you can opt-out of receiving these materials by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the materials or by contacting us directly at privacy@boostsoftware.com. This option does not apply to communications primarily for the purpose of administering orders, contracts, support, product safety warnings, software updates, or other administrative and transactional notices. If you would like to have your personal information, or software usage and machine information, removed from our records, you may contact us directly at privacy@boostsoftware.com

**How to Update Your Information:** Here are some ways you can modify the contact information that you have provided to us:

  * Email Newsletters: Should your email address change, you may manage your subscription by unsubscribing to our newsletter and re-subscribing with your new email address.
  * Specialized Areas: Specialized areas of our web site that require you to register may identify, at the point of collection, the ways available for you to update your information.

**Safeguarding Your Personal Information:** We recognize industry standards and employ security safeguards to protect information from unauthorized access and misuse. We use the most accurate and current information you provide in order to process your request. Furthermore, whenever you transmit sensitive information, such as credit card information, to us through our web site, we provide you access to our secure server that allows encryption across the Internet. Browsers offer varying degrees of security, particularly in regard to encryption. Even the same version of a browser can come with different levels of encryption. For your protection, make sure your browser is set and configured to support Secure Socket Layer (SSL) 2.0/3.0 and employs 128-bit encryption. All acceptable browsers do provide detailed information on security levels in "Properties" or "Document Information" from the browser's menu bar. See your browser's "Help" tab or documentation for more information.

If a password is used to help protect your accounts and personal information, it is your responsibility to keep your password confidential. Do not share this information with anyone. If you are sharing a computer with anyone, you should always log out before leaving a site or service to protect access to your information from subsequent users.

**Enforcement:** Boost regularly reviews its compliance with this Privacy Policy. Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this statement or Boost's treatment of personal information by contacting us at the link or address indicated below. 

**Cookies and Tracking Assets:** Boost uses various technologies to collect and store information when you acquire a Boost product, which may include one or more cookies sent to your device. We also use cookies when you interact with services offered by our partners related to the Boost products, such as product registration, support or related services. A "cookie" is a name for tokens of information that our web site may provide to your browser while you are at those sites. We use cookies to help us and our partners keep track of the referring website and to help our partners identify you as a Boost licensee when you register a Boost Product, or request support or an additional service. 

When you download a Boost product, we will assign you a unique identifier that may include machine and software usage information. Boost maintains a database that associates this identifier with the purchase and registration information you provide to our agents or us. This database is not disclosed to any non-Boost entity. 

If you simply want to browse, you do not have to accept cookies from the Boost Sites. Should you decide, however, that you would like to register and login to special areas of a Boost Site or purchase Boost products and you have modified your browser settings not to accept cookies, you will need to re-set your browser to accept the cookies that we send it. Otherwise, you may not be able to participate in certain areas of the Boost Sites or purchase Boost products. Most browsers are defaulted to accept and maintain cookies. These cookies are not tied to your personally identifiable information.

Third party vendors, including Google, may use cookies to serve ads to you while you are using the Boost Sites based on your prior visits. You may opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page.

Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to Boost Site users based on their visit to our sites and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Google Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/). Boost Site users may also opt out of all third party vendor's use of cookies for interest-based advertising by visiting aboutads.info.

**Links to Other Sites:** The Boost Sites often provide links to third-party web sites, such as those of our business partners and online advertisers. You should review their privacy policies to learn more about what, why, and how they collect and use personally identifiable information.

**For Questions or Concerns:** If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact privacy@BoostSoftware.com. Boost corporate headquarters are located at 75 Arlington Street, Suite 500, Boston, MA USA 02116.

**Changes to the Boost Privacy Statement:** Boost reserves the right to change this policy from time to time. If we do make changes, the revised Privacy Policy will be posted on this site. 

**NOTICE TO CHILDREN UNDER THE AGE OF 18 AND THEIR PARENTS OR LEGAL GUARDIANS:** THE BOOST SITES ARE INTENDED FOR ADULTS. WE DO NOT KNOWINGLY OR INTENTIONALLY COLLECT PERSONAL INFORMATION FROM ANYONE UNDER THE AGE OF 18. IF YOU ARE UNDER THE AGE OF 18, PLEASE DO NOT PROVIDE ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION TO BOOST SOFTWARE. IF YOU KNOW OF ANYONE UNDER THE AGE OF 18 WHO HAS PROVIDED US WITH INFORMATION, PLEASE CONTACT US IMMEDIATELY AND WE WILL REMOVE THE INFORMATION.

This Privacy Policy was last amended on 2013 Apr 22.
